哪里有娱乐？
Any entertainment there?
来啰！1999年 乔伊“快乐”的一年
All right. Here we go! 1999,the year of Joey.
恭喜你 怎么了？
We're very happy for you.What's the matter?
我们想在午夜接吻 但其他人都没这个打算
We wanted to kiss at midnight,but nobody else will,so....
好，交给我
All right,I'll take care of it.
乔伊，只剩30秒了 你能怎么办？
It's 30 seconds to midnight,what are you gonna do?
相信我好吗？
Will you just trust me?
33！32！31 罗斯…
Thirty-three,32,31
你0点要亲谁？ 瑞秋还是菲比？
Who are you kissing at midnight? Rachel or Phoebe?
什么？ 你得亲别人，又不能亲你妹妹
You can't kiss your sister.
那谁要亲我妹？ 钱德
-Who's gonna kiss my sister? -Chandler.
不会吧
Oh,man! Really?
老兄，你觉得谁比较好 我还是钱德？
Would you rather have me or him kiss her?
有道理
That's a good point.
我和瑞秋有太多纠葛 那就菲比吧
Since I have that whole history with Rachel,I guess Phoebe.
好
Okay
菲比！罗斯午夜想亲你
Phoebe! Listen. Ross wants to kiss you at midnight.
太明显了，他大可直说
So obvious. Why doesn't he just ask?
瑞秋！我午夜要亲你 什么？
-Rach! I'm gonna kiss you at midnight. -What?
大家都得找人亲 因为你俩的过去所以你不能亲罗斯
You can't kiss Ross. You got the history.
所以呢？ 所以你想让我亲还是让钱德亲
So?-Would you prefer me or Chandler?
有道理 对吧
-Good point.
3！2！1！新年快乐！
Three,two,one!Happy New Year!
新年快乐 新年快乐
-Happy New Year. -Happy New Year.
菲比，新年快乐 你也是
-Happy New Year. -You too.
乔伊，新年快乐
Happy New Year,Joey.
刚才那个吻如何？
So that do anything for you?
本集播出：“新年新希望”
The One with All the Resolutions
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
你们知道吗？我要召告天下 99年我不离婚
You know what?I'm gonna go out on a limb and say "No divorces in '99!"
但你的离婚手续还没办好
But your divorce isn't final yet.
99年我只离一次婚 漂亮
Just the one divorce in '99!
我今年要过得很快乐 我要让自己快乐
I am gonna be happy this year. I am gonna make myself happy.
你要我们回避吗？
Do you want us to leave the room?
我每天都要做一件没做过的事
Every day I am gonna do one thing I have never done before.
这就是我的新年新希望
That is my New Year's resolution.
好棒的希望 我是想开大型客机
That's a good one!Mine is to pilot a commercial jet.
这个也很棒，接着你得找一群
Now you only have to find a planeload of people...
希望自己坠机身亡的人
...whose resolution is to plummet to their deaths.
也许你应该立志不取笑朋友
Maybe your resolution should be not to make fun of your friends.
尤其是会免费载你去欧洲的人
Especially the ones who might fly you to Europe for free.
她开飞机的机率 比你不取笑我们还高
She has a better chance of flying up your nose...than you do of not making fun of us.
50元赌你无法1年不笑我们
I'll bet $50 you can't go the year without making fun of us.
干脆1星期好了 我赌了
Better yet,a week.I'll take that bet,my friend.
输我那50元 就可以当你的“每日新鲜事”
Paying me the $50 can be...the "new thing you do" that day.
就从现在开始
And it starts right now!
我的新年新希望是学吉他
My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play guitar.
真的？为什么？
Really? How come?
我的履历表 不是列了一堆特殊专长吗
You know those special skills I have listed on my resume?
我希望有一项是真的
I would love it if one of those was true.
你要我教你吗？ 我是个很好的老师
Want me to teach you? I'm a great teacher.
真的？你教过谁？
Really? Who have you taught?
我教过我，我很喜欢我
Well,I taught me. And I loved me.
太好了，谢谢你
That'd be great! Yeah,thanks,Phoebe.
我希望自己不要那么洁癖
My resolution is to be less obsessed with being neat and clean.
是吗？
Really?
不要
No
换一个好了
Or something else.
布莱儿忘了把眼镜带走 她需要这副眼镜来盯住男朋友
Look. Blaire forgot her glasses.She'll need these to keep an eye on that boyfriend.
听说她男朋友得把订书机收在抽屉里 你们懂我的意思吧
Who,from what I hear,needs to keep his stapler...in his desk drawer,if you know what I mean!
或许你应该让自己别那么八卦
Maybe your resolution should be to gossip less.
我哪有八卦
What? I don't gossip.
或许我偶尔会发现一些事 或听到一些事，然后转述出去
Maybe sometimes I find out things.Or I hear something and I pass that information on.
当做一种公众服务
You know,kind of like a public service.
这并不代表我很八卦 你们会说泰德·科佩尔（主持人）八卦吗？
It doesn't mean I'm a gossip. Is Ted Koppel a gossip?
如果他说同事隆胸失败的话 我会的
If Ted Koppel talked about his coworkers' botched boob jobs,I would.
她隆成这样耶
They were like this!
好，我的新年新希望 就是不八卦
Fine,my New Year's resolution will be not to gossip.
这还不简单 简单？你从来没做到过
-It's easy. -Easy? You have never kept a resolution.
我当然有 好，来看看你去年的表现
-Yes,I have. -Okay,let's see how you did last year.
不要拿我的日记 你不能看我的日记
No. No. Not my diary. You cannot read my diary.
亲爱的日记：我好兴奋 我的新年新希望是每天写你
"Dear diary: I'm so excited.My resolution is to write in you every day.
我们明天见
See you tomorrow."
什么都没写
Nothing.
去年没发生什么事
You know,not a lot happened last year.
好，我这次会证明给你们看 我再也不八卦了
All right,I will prove to you that I can keep it this time. No more gossiping.
我恨八卦，国中时
I hate gossip. In junior high...
有个女生说了我很多坏话 我就放火烧她的脚踏车
this girl said a lot of mean stuff about me and I set her bike on fire.
她说你什么？ 她说我太疯狂了
-Wow,what did she say about you? -She said I was crazy.
得到报应了吧
But I guess she got hers.
“中央咖啡馆”
那就明天见 好
-I'll see you tomorrow. -Okay.
我约刚才那个女生出去 很好
I just asked that girl out.Nice!
这算是你今天的新鲜事吗？
Is that part of your "new thing" for today?
没错，你们看
Yes,it is. See?
伊丽莎白…逗你玩？
"Elizabeth...Hornswoggle"?
对…伊丽莎白逗你玩
That's right.Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
逗你玩
Hornswoggle
你还好吗？ 这个姓有哪里好笑吗？
You okay,Chandler?Something funny about that name?
没有，我只是觉得以前好像听过
No,I just think I've heard it somewhere before.
是吗？在哪里听过？ 一定是个很好笑的地方
Oh,really? Where?Somewhere funny,I'll bet.
菲比 知道吗
Guess what.
我要跟一个伊丽莎白逗你玩约会
I have a date with Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
逗你玩？你的嘴一定很痒
Hornswoggle？Oh,this must be killing you!
才不会
Not really.
我还没说她中间的名字 拜托不要
-I haven't told you her middle name yet. -Well,don't. Just don't.
待会见
-See you later. -See you.
菲比，我可以上第一课了 好
All right,Phoebe,I am ready for my first lesson.
不行，不能碰吉他
No,you don't touch the guitar.
先练手，再练琴
First you learn here,then here.
好吧
Okay
好，第一课，和弦
Lesson one: Chords.
我不知道这些和弦的真正名称
Now,I don't know the actual names of the chords.
不过我照手势帮它们取了名字
But I made up names for the way my hand looks while I'm doing them.
所以这是熊爪…
So then this is "Bear Claw."
火鸡脚…
"Turkey Leg"...
和老太太
...and "Old Lady."
真有趣的吉他教学方式
What an interesting approach to guitar instruction.
有些人可能会觉得好笑 我觉得很普通
You know,some might find it amusing. I myself find it regular.
各位，瑞秋今天很乖 她都没有八卦
Hey,everybody!Rachel was so good today. She didn't gossip at all.
没错，即使我发现…
I didn't. Even when I found out
总之我发现了某人的某件事 但是我不会说出来
Let's say I found out something about someone...and let's just say.she's gonna keep it
菲比，你看
Check this out.
你搞定老太太了
You nailed the Old Lady!
我觉得我进步了 就在回家的路上去吉他店…
I thought I was getting better,so I stopped by this guitar store
你在店里有碰吉他吗？
Did you touch any of the guitars there?
有吗？
Did you?
没有
No.
手给我
Give me your hands.
琴弦，这一只手
Strings.
弹片
Pick.
你想学吉他吗？ 想啊
-Do you want to learn to play guitar? -Yes.
那就不要碰吉他
Then don't touch one!
班 莫妮卡姑姑
-Hi,Ben. -Auntie Monica!
罗斯穿皮裤
Ross is wearing leather pants!
没有人看见罗斯穿皮裤吗？
Does nobody else see Ross is wearing leather pants?
谁来说句话吧
Someone comment on the pants!
很帅气啊 我很喜欢
-I think they're very nice. -I really like them a lot.
我想的不是这个
Not what I had in mind.
罗斯这种人通常不穿这种裤子
People like Ross don't wear these types of pants.
这种裤子很紧
You see,they're very tight.
也许可以评论一下这个地方
Maybe there's something in that area?
很好看啊
I think they look really good.
在哪里买的？
Where'd you get them?
我还没做今天的新鲜事
I needed a new thing for today.
我一直觉得这家皮衣店很香
There's this leather store that always smells so good.
于是我心想 我从来没买过一条很香的皮裤
And I thought to myself: "Wow. I've never owned...a really good-smelling pair of pants before."
拜托啦！
Oh,come on!
说真的，你们觉得怎样？
What do you think?
好怪 难看死了
You look like a freak.Awful!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
这是我的新年新希望 把我儿子弄瞎？
-It's my New Year's resolution. -To blind my child?
不，是多照照我们的相片
To take pictures of us together.
我觉得这样最好 大家都会喜欢
It's the best resolution. Everyone can enjoy them.
大家也都会喜欢我的演奏
Everyone will enjoy my music as well.
天哪，这条裤子热死了
My God,these pants! I'm burning up.
她现在靠过来是想让我死吗？ 这里面跟火山一样
Oh God! She wants to snuggle now? Is she trying to kill me?It's like a volcano in here!
你热吗？ 不会
-Are you hot? -No.
那就是我在热
It must just be me,then.
那是裤子跟沙发磨擦的声音
That was just the pants and the couch.
可以借用一下洗手间吗？
Do you mind if I use your bathroom?
请便 谢谢
-Go ahead. -Thanks.
我最喜欢的部分要来了 好
My favorite part's coming up!
完蛋了
Oh,my God!
老虎，恐龙，冰山
Tiger.Dragon.Iceberg!
乔瑟夫，你昨晚有练习吗？
Joseph,did you even study at all last night?
我有啊 那就把冰山做出来
Yes,I did!Then do lceberg.
升G 升G？
G-sharp.G-sharp?
你在偷学和弦名称吗？
Have you been studying the real names of the chords?
有没有？
Have you?
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
怎样？我又没有碰吉他 但是你质疑我的教学方式
What? I didn't touch a guitar!But you're questioning my method!
我不是质疑 我根本就觉得很蠢
No,I'm not questioning it. I'm saying it's stupid!
什么？
What?
谢谢
Thank you.
其他学生都不觉得我蠢
You know,none of my other student....thought I was stupid.
你的其他学生就是你
Your other student was you!
那又怎样，也许你应该更用功
Well,maybe you just need to try a little harder!
也许我应该找个正牌老师
Maybe I need to try a real teacher!
这里，安迪古柏（音乐家），他在教吉他 这里还有他跟小朋友的合照
Here! Andy Cooper. He teaches guitar.There's a picture of him with a kid.
小朋友拿着吉他
And the kid's got a guitar!
好，你去跟你的专业老师学
Fine!You learn from your "qualified instructor."
等大家听腻“坏蛋李洛布朗” 你可别哭着来找我
But don't come crying when everyone is sick...of hearing you play "Bad,Bad Leroy Brown"!
全城最坏的大坏蛋
Baddest man in the whole damn town
好啊，你去帮他啊
Oh,fine. Take his side!
我好想赶快去找你
I can't wait to be with you.
罗斯把小孩接走我就溜过去
I'll sneak over as soon as I can.
我会告诉瑞秋 我要洗两个小时衣服
I'll tell Rachel I'll be doing laundry.
洗衣服？那是我的新绰号吗？
Laundry. Is that my new nickname?
不是，你明知你的绰号是大雕
You know what your nickname is,Mr. Big
别再那样看我了 菲比是个烂老师
Would you stop looking at me like that? Phoebe was a terrible teacher.
我什么都没学到 我也很难过…
I wasn't learning anything from her
算了，讲来讲去都一样
Look I feel bad,too Forget it,we're going around in circles.
走开啦
Go
喂？
Hello
乔伊，我是罗斯，我需要帮忙
Joey,it's Ross. I need some help.
钱德不在 你可以帮我
Chandler's not here.You can help me.
好
Okay
我在伊丽莎白的浴室里
I'm in Elizabeth's bathroom.
很好啊
Nice!
不是，我觉得皮裤很热 就进来脱掉
No,I got really hot in my pants,so I took them off.
结果它一定是遇汗缩水 或是我的腿因热膨胀
But they must have shrunk from the sweat.Or my legs expanded from the heat.
我现在穿不回去了
I can't get them back on,Joey. I can't!
这个情况蛮严重的
That is quite a situation.
你有粉之类的东西吗？
Do you see any powder?
有，我有爽身粉
Powder! Yeah,I have powder.
很好，把它撒在腿上吸汗 就能把裤子穿回去了
Good,good.Sprinkle some on. It'll absorb moisture.Then you can get your pants on.
好，等一下
Yeah,hold on.
裤子还是拉不上来
They're not coming on,man.
好，把裤子割破几刀再穿回去
Okay,cut slits in the pants,right? Then put them back on...
然后出去告诉她你是绿巨人
...go out there and tell her you're the lncredible Hulk.
钱德不在是吧？
Chandler's not there?
那样真的可以，不过算了
That would have worked,but all right,fine.
你找得到凡士林吗？
You see any.... Oh,Vaseline?
我找到乳液，我有乳液 乳液行吗？
I see lotion. I have lotion. Will that work?
行，把它涂在腿上 等一下
Sure,throw some of that on there.Hold on.
听起来有用
Sounds like it's working.
裤子还是拉不上来 而且乳液和爽身粉糊成一团
They're still not coming on,man.And the lotion and the powder have made a paste.
是喔？什么颜色？
Really.What color is it?
什么颜色有差别吗？
What difference does that make?
如果跟裤子的颜色一样
If the paste matches the pants,you can make paste pants...
你就糊一条假裤子 她就看不出来了
...and she won't know!
乔伊，你有空吗？
Do you have a minute?
我该怎么…
Dude,what am l
瑞秋来了，祝你好运 让我知道结果
Rachel's here,so good luck. Let me know how it goes.
乔伊，我遇到天大的问题
Joey,I have such a problem.
你来得正好，我正在到处救火
Your timing couldn't be better.I'm putting out fires all over the place.
好，乔伊，我得告诉你一件事
I have got to tell you something.
什么事？
What is it?
天哪，这件事太严重了 但你得保证不说出去
It's so huge! But promise me. You cannot tell anyone.
不要，我不想知道
No,no,no! I don't want to know.
你绝对想知道，太不可思议了
You do want to know. This is unbelievable!
我不管，我不想再当知道秘密 却不能说的人
I'm tired of being the guy who knows all the secrets...and can't tell anyone.
什么秘密？你知道什么秘密？
You know secrets?
你不该八卦的
You're not supposed to gossip!
我知道，但这件事我憋不住 我刚才拿起电话…
I can't keep this in. So I pick up the phone
我不听
I'm not listening to you!
罗斯，你进去很久了
You've been in there for a long time.
我开始有点害怕了
I'm starting to get kind of freaked out.
好，我要出去了
All right,I'm coming out.
你可以把灯关掉吗？
Hey,can you turn the lights off?
不行，灯就让它开着
Let's just leave the lights on.
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
我出了一点状况
I had a problem.
菲比
Phoebe
我不能跟你说话 我没在电话簿上登广告
I can't talk to you. I don't have a fancy ad in the yellow pages.
菲比，你听我说…
Look Phoebe，I just
我为批评你的教法道歉
I want to apologize for saying your method was stupid.
我也想重新拜你为师
And maybe ask you to be my teacher again?
在你说可以之前 我绝对不碰吉他
I promise,I won't touch a guitar until you say I'm ready.
我真的可以了？
You really think I'm ready?
酷毙了
Wow,cool!
那个和弦弹对了吗？ 不对
-Was the chord at least right before -No.
我的上帝啊
Oh,my God!
我们听说了，好惨
We heard about your pants. I'm so sorry.
今年应该很美好才对
This year was supposed to be great.
才第二天我就成了 穿不合身的皮裤的逊人
It's only the second day and I'm a loser...with stupid leather pants that don't even fit!
没这回事 你不逊
You're not a loser.
你们看我
Look at me!
你看，班画了你的画像
Hey,look!Ben drew a picture of you.
你是牛仔喔
You're a cowboy.
因为我穿皮裤？
Because of the leather pants?
班并不觉得你逊 他觉得你是牛仔，很棒吧
He thinks you're a cowboy,not a loser. That's something.
真的很棒 你好，伙计（方言）
-lt really is something. -Howdy,partner.
也许我应该再去买一条
Maybe I should get another pair.
他们有一些侧边有流苏的
You know,they had some...with fringe all down the sides.
菲比，这种怪事你可能会知道 脑浆的沸点是几度？
Phoebe,you may know this. You know strange things.What is the boiling point of brain?
我以前知道
I used to know this.
我去跟班说晚安
I'm gonna go kiss Ben good night.
他居然觉得我是牛仔
I can't believe he thinks I'm a cowboy.
我会是个好牛仔
I would make a good cowboy.
好，既然没事 我要去洗衣服了
Now that everything's wrapped up,I'll do my laundry.
我也是，如果这一件脏了的话
Yeah,me too. If this shirt is dirty.
是的
Yep
我也要走了
I'm going to the airport.
我要去机场，只要等久一点 应该能逮到没人管的飞机
If I hang around there long enough...someone's bound to leave a plane unattended.
祝你好运 再见
-Good luck,honey. -Bye.
乔伊 记得我要说的那件大事吗？
Remember that thing I was gonna tell you about?
我不会告诉你 但如果你自己发现
I won't tell you. But if you found out on your own...
那就没关系 我们就可以讨论了对吧？
...that would be okay and we could talk about it.
那样就不是秘密，的确没关系
Well,then it wouldn't be a secret. So that would be okay.
乔伊，你去钱德的房间 把我借给他的书拿回来好吗？
Would you mind going into Chandler's bedroom...and getting that book he borrowed from me?
现在？你要我现在去？ 对
Now? You want me to go over there now?
你知道什么吗？ 你知道什么吗？
-Do you know something? -Do you?
我或许知道 我也是
-I might know something. -I might too.
你知道什么？ 不行，你先说我才能说
-What do you know? -You tell me first.
我不能说 那我也不能说
-I can't. -Then I can't.
那好吧
Okay,fine.
你才不知道
You don't know.
不如我现在就去钱德的房间 就可以知道我想的确实没错
I'll walk into his bedroom and see the thing...I think I know is actually the thing I think I know!
你知道 你也知道
-You know! -And you know!
对，我知道
Yeah,I know!
钱德和莫妮卡？ 真叫人不敢相信
Chandler and Monica? Oh,this is unbelievable!
你知道多久了？ 太久了
-How long have you known? -Too long!
天哪，我早就想找人说了
I've been dying to talk to someone about this!
听着，我们不能告诉别人 他们两个好紧张…
You can't say anything to anybody. They're so weird about that.
菲比
Phoebe
在下雨，我不想在下雨天飞
It's raining.I don't like to fly in the rain.
我要去雨中漫步
I am gonna go for a walk in the rain.
我也要
Me too.
怪人
That's weird.
他们一定有一腿
I bet they're doing it.
好，我憋不住受不了了
Okay,look. I can't take it anymore.
你赢，好吗？拿去
So you win. Okay? Here.
菲比，开飞机？ 不如开太空船回你的星球去
Flying a jet? Make it a spaceship...so you can get back to your home planet!
罗斯，有你的电话 汤姆琼斯（六十年代英国歌星）跟你要他的裤子
Phone call for you. Tom Jones. He wants his pants back!
逗你玩？ 你在跟《弗雷格尔星》里的角色（名字都很怪）约会吗？
And Hornswoggle? What,are you dating a character from Fraggle Rock?